Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- Cornell University Related Materials, 1917-1931
  - Agricultural Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Agronomy, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Architecture, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Botany, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Botany, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Business Office, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Chemistry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Publications, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Library, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Office, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Comptroller, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Comptroller, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Steam Reports, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Agricultural Council, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Agricultural Council, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Veterinary Council, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Dairy Industry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Dairy Industry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Dairy Industry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Dairy Industry, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Engineering, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Entomology, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Entomology, 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Willson, R. B., 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Allen, A. A., 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Extension, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Extension, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Extension, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Director of Extension, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Faculty- Agriculture, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Faculty - University, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Farm Bureau, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Farm Practice, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Forestry, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Forestry, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Home Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Meek, H. B. & Randolph, F. H., 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Information Service, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Information Service, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Notice of Extension of Publications, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Law College, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Library - College, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Library - University, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Medical College, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Meteorology, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Music Department, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Plant Breeding, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Plant Breeding, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Plant Pathology, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    Thomas, H. E.
  - Pomology, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Poultry, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - President's Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - President's Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - President's Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - President's Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - President's Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Purchasing Office, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Registrar, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Rural Education, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Rural Education, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Rural Education, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Rural Engineering, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Rural Organization, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Secretary - College, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Betten, Cornelius, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Secretary - University, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Treasurer, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - University Christian Association, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Veterinary College, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Zoology, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Abstracts, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Agronomy, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Architecture, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Botany, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Business Office, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Publications, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Alumni Office, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Comptroller - University, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Dairy Industry, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Dairy Industry, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Engineering, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Entomology, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - Entomology, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Willson, R. B., 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Extension, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 86)
    Cook, D. S.
  - Extension, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 88)
  - University Faculty, 1925-1926 (Box 35, Folder 89)
  - Farm Bureau, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Coryell, J.
  - Farm Practice, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Floriculture, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Forestry, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Meek, H. B., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Information, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Information, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Law, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Library, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - University Library, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Medical, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Meteorology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Music, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Plant Breeding, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Plant Breeding, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Plant Pathology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Plant Pathology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Plant Pathology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Plant Pathology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Pomology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - President's Office, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - President's Office, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Purchasing Office, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Registrar, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Rural Education, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Kruse, P. J.
    Palmer, E. L.
  - Rural Education, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Rural Education, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Rural Engineering, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    Felton, R. A.
  - Secretary's Office, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Cornelius Betten, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Secretary - University, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Treasurer, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - University Christian Association, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Veterinary College, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Zoology, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    Maynard, L. A.
  - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Agronomy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Agronomy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Agronomy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Agronomy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Architecture, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Attorney - University, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Botany, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Botany, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Botany, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 56)
    Curtis, C. E.
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 58)
  - Buildings and Grounds Heating Situation, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 59)
  - Business Office, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 60)
  - Business Office, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 61)
  - Chemistry, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 62)
  - Publications, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - Alumni Office, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 64)
  - Comptroller - University, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 65)
  - Comptroller - University, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 66)
  - Comptroller - University, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 67)
  - Steam Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 68)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 69)
  - Agriculture, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 70)
  - Veterinary, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 89)
  - Dairy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 90)
    Guthrie, E. S.
  - Dairy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 91)
  - Dairy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 92)
  - Dairy, 1926-1927 (Box 37, Folder 93)
  - Dairy, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Entomology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Entomology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Extension, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Extension, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Extension, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Faculty - Agriculture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Faculty - University, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Farm Bureau, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Coryell, Joy
  - Farm Bureau, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Farm Practice, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Farm Practice, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Farm Practice, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Horticulture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Horticulture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Horticulture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Horticulture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Forestry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Forestry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Forestry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Forestry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Letters, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Meek, H. B., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Meek, H. B., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Meek, H. B., 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Information, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Information, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Information, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Law, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Library - Agriculture, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Library - University, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Medical, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Meteorology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Plant Breeding, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Plant Breeding, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Plant Breeding, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Plant Breeding, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 46)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 48)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Plant Pathology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Pomology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Pomology, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Poultry, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  - President's Office, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  - Purchasing, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  - Registrar, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  - Rural Education, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  - Rural Education, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  - Rural Education, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  - Rural Education, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  - Rural Education, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  - Rural Engineering, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  - Rural Engineering, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 76)
    Sanderson, E. D.
    Duthie, Mary Eva
  - Rural Social Organization, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  - Rural Social Organization, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  - Secretary - College, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - Betten - Cornelius, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - Treasurer, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 89)
  - University Christian Association, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 90)
  - University Christian Association, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 91)
  - University Christian Association, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 92)
  - University Christian Association, 1926-1927 (Box 38, Folder 93)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Vegetable Gardening, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Veterinary, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Veterinary, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Zoology, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Agronomy, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Animal Husbandry, Head of, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Animal Husbandry, Head of, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Animal Husbandry, Head of, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Architecture, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Arts and Sciences, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Attorney - University, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Botany, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Botany, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Botany, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Botany, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Curtis, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Business Office, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Business Office, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Business Office, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Alumni Office, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Comptroller, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Steam Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Steam Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - Cornell Countryman, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Agricultural Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 60)
  - Agricultural Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 62)
  - Agricultural Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Home Economics Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 64)
  - Veterinary Council, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 65)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 66)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 67)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 68)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 70)
  - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 71)
  - Engineering, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 72)
  - Entomology, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 73)
    Allen, Arthur A.
    Embody, G. C.
  - Entomology, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 74)
  - Entomology, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 75)
  - Entomology, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 76)
  - Extension, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 77)
  - Extension, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 78)
  - Extension, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 79)
  - Extension, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 80)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 81)
  - Phillips, E. F., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 82)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 83)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 84)
  - Ladd, C. E., 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 85)
  - Agricultural Faculty, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 86)
  - University Faculty, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 87)
  - Farm Bureau, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 88)
    Underwood, E. Victor
  - Farm Bureau, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 89)
  - Farm Practice, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Farm Practice, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Floriculture, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Floriculture, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Floriculture, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Floriculture, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Forestry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Forestry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Forestry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Forestry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Forestry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Levels, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Levels, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Heads of Departments and Circular Levels, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Home Economics, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Meek, H. B., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Meek, H. B., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Meek, H. B., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - Meek, H. B., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Information, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Information, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Information, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Law, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - College Library, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - University Library, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Medical, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - Meteorology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Music, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Plant Breeding, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    Fraser, Allan C.
  - Plant Breeding, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Plant Breeding, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Plant Pathology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Plant Pathology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Plant Pathology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - Plant Pathology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - Pomology, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Poultry Husbandry, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - Boochever, L. C., 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - President's Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - Purchasing Office, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Registrar, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - Rural Education, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 72)
    Kruse, Paul J.
  - Rural Education, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - Rural Education, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - Rural Education, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - Rural Education, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - Rural Engineering, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - Rural Engineering, 1927-1928 (Box 43, Folder 78)